RESUME

C.Wesley

Administrative Work

- A

Profile:

I have administrative qualification with 26 years of work experience in World Vision India. I have worked at different districts of Tamil Nadu. Due to role redundancy I am seeking a new job opportunity. I wish to apply for **Administrative work** in your company and eager to serve with hard work and dedication. I am willing to work in Coimbatore, Tiruppur, Pollachi and Erode districts.

Personal Details:

Date of Birth – 06/07/1968 Gender - Male Nationality – Indian Marital Status - Married

Contact Address:

184/F, Pennycuick Nagar, 3rd South Cross Street, Theni – 625 531 Cell No - +91 9994213675 Links – Gmail – wesley671968@gmail.com

Employment History:

Coordinator Sponsorship Effectiveness at World Vision India, 7years was on Contract and the next 19years on Payroll. Worked at Coonoor, Madurai, Salem, Theni, Pudukottai and Manapparai branches.
From – February 1997 – May 2023

World Vision is one of the child focused humanitarian organization with proven effective work in community development, sponsorship and relief practices empowering vulnerable children. I was working in Sponsorship Department in facilitating and translating correspondence from children to sponsors helping the sponsorship process.

I am experienced in managing Office correspondence ensuring proper documentation, track mails in Outlook / Courier, and maintain filing system of HR Records, Payroll, Staff Leave Records etc. Also in Generating Reports, Stationery stock management, Insurance work, Petty cash and Software backup.

Trainee Assistant at George Oakes Limited, Madurai
 From – August 1995 – July 1996

George Oakes Limited is a Tractor Assembly Company. I was working in Administration Department in preparing Invoice, Bills, GRN – Goods Receipt cum Inspection Note for the Tractor spare parts received from various places.

Education

- ➤ MSW Master of Social Work Annamalai University, Chidambaram.

 June 2008 April 2009 with 59% marks
- PGD PM&IR Post Graduate Diploma in Personnel Management and Industrial Relations - Madurai Kamaraj University, Madurai. June 1991 – March 1993 with 53% marks
- BBA Bachelor of Business Administration S.Vellaichamy Nadar College Madurai. June 1988 – March 1991 with 60% marks

Skills:

- 1) Computer skills proficient in MS office, word, excel, powerpoint and outlook
- 2) Interpersonal and communication skills
- 3) Tally Prime accounting
- 4) Typing and data entry skills
- 5) Translation from Tamil to English
- 6) Planning and Organisational skills

Competencies:

- ✓ Knowledge in office administration
- ✓ Attention to detail and accuracy
- √ Time management abilities
- ✓ Able to work independently and also with a Team
- ✓ Ability to adapt to changing priorities

<u>Languages:</u>

Tamil – Read – Write – Speak English – Read – Write – Speak

If I get an opportunity I will perform the duties and responsibilities as per the expectation of your organization. I will be helpful to you in your sustained development and innovative initiatives of your company. Thank you.

Yours Sincerely,

C. Wosley.